[
	{
		"difficulty":"easy",
		"question":"The national animal of India is ",
		"answer":"Tiger",
		"points":10
	},
	
	{
		"difficulty":"easy",
		"question":"The national bird of India is ",
		"answer":"Peacock",
		"points":10
	},

	{
		"difficulty":"easy",
		"question":"The largest animal on land is ",
		"answer":"Elephant",
		"points":10
	},

	{
		"difficulty":"medium",
		"question":"I enjoy eating leaves and have an extremely long neck. What am I?",
		"answer":"Giraffe",
		"points":20
	},

	{
		"difficulty":"medium",
		"question":"I have a lush mane and am a predator in the jungle. What am I?",
		"answer":"Lion",
		"points":20
	},

	{
		"difficulty":"medium",
		"question":"I have black and white stripes on my body and enjoy eating grass. What am I?",
		"answer":"Zebra",
		"points":20
	},

	{
		"difficulty":"medium",
		"question":"I am a man's best friend. Who am I?",
		"answer":"Dog",
		"points":20
	},

	{
		"difficulty":"medium",
		"question":"I have black feathers and often fly in flocks. What am I?",
		"answer":"Crow",
		"points":20
	},

	{
		"difficulty":"hard",
		"question":"The bird that cannot fly is ",
		"answer":"Ostrich",
		"points":30
	},
	
	{
		"difficulty":"hard",
		"question":"I have 8 tentacles and am a predator in the ocean. Who am I?",
		"answer":"Octopus",
		"points":30
	},

	{
		"difficulty":"medium",
		"question":"I have 8 legs and weave beautiful webs. What am I?",
		"answer":"Spider",
		"points":20
	},

	{
		"difficulty":"medium",
		"question":"I have beautiful white feathers and am found in lakes. Who am I?",
		"answer":"Swan",
		"points":20
	},

	{
		"difficulty":"hard",
		"question":"I carry heavy loads and am related to horses. Who am I?",
		"answer":"Donkey",
		"points":30
	},

	{
		"difficulty":"medium",
		"question":"Which bird was used as a symbol of peace?",
		"answer":"Dove",
		"points":20
	},

	{
		"difficulty":"hard",
		"question":"I eat dead bodies and travel in packs. Who am I?",
		"answer":"Hyena",
		"points":30
	},

	{
		"difficulty":"hard",
		"question":"I can twist my neck by 270 degrees. Who am I?",
		"answer":"Owl",
		"points":30
	},

	{
		"difficulty":"easy",
		"question":"I drink milk and eat mice",
		"answer":"Cat",
		"points":10
	}


]
		









